Guide to the Frank Moore Papers MSS.135
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Oversize Materials: Series II.D: Other Artist Art Files
  - Mueller, Cookie, undated (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Nahas, Nabil, undated (Folder 6 Left)
  - Torres, Felix Gonzalez [located in map case], undated (Folder 2)
  - Sarfati, Patrick, undated (Folder 3 Left)
  - Self, Jim, 1981-2000 (Box 49, Folder 19)
  - Self, Jim- Cunningham Studio, undated (Box 50, Folder 19)
  - Self, Jim at Jacob's Pillow, undated (Box 50, Folder 20)
  - Smith, Jack, undated (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - Sperone, Gian Enzo, undated (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Steinbach, Haim, undated (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Tzaig, Uri, undated (Folder 5 Left)
  - Warren, Rosanna, undated (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Winokur, Neil, undated (Folder 4 Left, Folder 1)
  - Wojnarowicz, David, undated (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - Z[inlin], undated (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Group Exhibitions, undated (Box 69)
  - Group Exhibitions (Folder 13)
  - Miscellaneous: Photo Portrait of F. Moore, undated (Box 68, Folder 5)
- Oversize Materials: Series III.A: Correspondence
  These boxes contain oversize materials from Series III.A: Correspondence
  - AIDS Treatment Project, 1991 (Box 69)
  - Contemporary Arts Center, undated (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - Leibowitz, Cary, 1994-1995 (Box 68, Folder 8)
- Oversize Materials: Series IV.A: Magazines
  These boxes contain oversize materials from Series IV.A: Magazines
  - Hoard's Dairyman, 1992-1995 (Box 68, Folder 10)
  - Hoard's Dairyman, 1995-1996 (Box 68, Folder 9)
- Oversize Materials: Series IV.B: Catalogues and Manuals
  These boxes contain oversize materials from Series IV.B: Catalogues and Manuals
  - Decor: Moulding and Supply, undated (Box 50, Folder 1)
- Oversize Materials: Series IV.C: Clippings, Articles and Subject Files
  These boxes contain oversize materials from Series IV.C: Clippings, Articles and Subject Files
  - Cowboys, 1998 (Folder 3 Right)
  - Treaty Oak, 1995-1997 (Box 50, Folder 7)
- Oversize Materials: Series IV.D: Images
  These boxes contain oversize materials from Series IV.D: Images
  - Ken Brown Wrapping Paper, undated (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - DNA Cup, ink jet on foam board [located in map case], undated (Folder 1)
  - East Asian Flower Painting, undated (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - "Emigrants" images, gridded, undated (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous Images, undated (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Niagara Images, undated (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Wallpaper, 1999 (Box 69)
- Oversize Materials: Series IV.E: Photographs
  These boxes contain oversize materials from Series IV.E: Photographs
  - Panoramic Photographs of Niagara Falls, undated (Folder 4 Right)
- Oversize Materials: Series IV.F: Ephemera
  These boxes contain oversize materials from Series IV.F: Ephemera
  - Birds to Color by Number, undated (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Deep in the Rockies scrapbook, undated (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Paper Dolls, undated (Box 51, Folder 4)
- Oversize Materials: Series IV.G: Books
  These boxes contain oversize materials from Series IV.G: Books
  - The Original Watercolor Paintings by John James Audobon for The Birds of America, 1966 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - The National Audubon Society Collection, North American Trees, 1984 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Doubilet, David, Pacific: An undersea journey, 1992 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Geist, Valerius, Buffalo Nation: History and legend of the North America Bison, 1996 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Wolberg, Lewis R., Micro-Art: Art images in a hidden world, undated (Box 52, Folder 2)
- Oversize Materials: Series V.D: Production Materials, Boston Ballet and Cornell University Theater
  These boxes contain oversize materials from Series V.D: Production Materials, Boston Ballet and Cornell University Theater
  - Boston Ballet Repertory Lights, sound and stage plots [located in map case], undated (Folder 3)
  - Cornell University Theater Map [located in map case], undated (Folder 4)
- Oversize Materials: Series V.E: Promotional Materials
  These boxes contain oversize materials from Series V.E: Promotional Materials
  - Beehive Posters, French Production, additional larger posters in map case, undated (Folder 5)
  - Boston Ballet Posters, undated (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Sightlines: A Publication of the Boston Ballet, undated (Box 63, Folder 22)
  - Beehive Performance Posters, 1991 Dance Concert at Cornell University (Box 63, Folder 21)
- Oversize Materials: Series V.F: Artifacts
  These boxes contain oversize materials from Series V.F: Artifacts
  - Study for Hand and Forearm, undated (Box 63, Folder 20)
- Oversize Materials: Series VI.C: Miller's Wife Production Materials
  These boxes contain oversize materials from Series VI.C: Miller's Wife Production Materials
  - Realty Newspapers, 1988 (Box 63, Folder 19)
  - Time Chart, undated (Box 53, Folder 6)
- Oversize Materials: Series VIII.A: Personal Items
  These boxes contain oversize materials from Series VIII.A: Personal Items
  - X-rays, foot and toes, 1977 (Box 63, Folder 18)
  - X-rays, chest and lungs, 1977 (Box 63, Folder 17)
  - X-rays, lungs and chest, 1977, 1978 (Box 63, Folder 16)
  - X-rays, chest, 1977 (Box 63, Folder 15)
  - X-rays, chest, 1978 (Box 63, Folder 14)
  - X-rays, chest, 1979 (Box 63, Folder 13)
  - X-rays, nasal bones, 1980 (Box 63, Folder 12)
- Oversize Materials: Series VIII.B: Art Implements and Artifacts
  These boxes contain oversize materials from Series VIII.B: Art Implements and Artifacts
  - Acetate cutouts, undated (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - Acetates used in "Arena", 1992 (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - Acetate #19, used in "Debutante" [located in map case], 1992 (Folder 14)
  - Acetate #20 used in "Clinical Trial" and "Debutante", 1991 (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Acetate #21, used in "Debutante", 1992 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Acetates used in "Eclipse" and rectal pear cutouts. Group envelope #3 and Acetates #25, undated (Box 53, Folder 19)
  - Layout Boards and Transparencies for Unidentified Works, undated (Flat-file-folder 2 Left, Flat-file-folder 1 Right, Flat-file-folder 2 Right)
  - Rectal pear, undated (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Opaque material, undated (Box 53, Folder 21)
  - Publicity photo and acetates, undated (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Rub on lettering, undated (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Smoke prints, undated (Box 53, Folder 24)
  - Stencils, grapes, orange, semi-circle, undated (Box 53, Folder 25)
- Oversize Materials: Series VIII.C: Miscellaneous
  These boxes contain oversize materials from Series VIII.C: Miscellaneous
  - Paper fragments found at the World Trade Center, September 13, 2001 (Box 63, Folder 6)
- Oversize Materials: Series IX.A: Juvenalia
  These boxes contain oversize materials from Series IX.A: Juvenalia
  - Yale Diploma, 1975 (Box 63, Folder 5)
- Oversize Materials: Series X.A: Brochures, Merchandise Catalogues, and Owner's Manuals.
  These boxes contain oversize materials from Series X.A: Brochures, Merchandise Catalogues, and Owner's Manuals.
  - La Passion du Christ, 1975 (Box 63, Folder 4)
- Oversize Materials: Series X.B: Catalogues
  These boxes contain oversize materials from Series X.B: Catalogues
  - Sagacho Exhibit Space, Dui Seid, 1994 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - American Fashion Awards, 2000 (Box 63, Folder 2)
- Oversize Materials: Series X.C: Periodicals
  These boxes contain oversize materials from Series X.C: Periodicals
  - East Village Eye, April 1984 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - National Campaign for Freedom of Expression Bulletin(summer 1994) (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - New York Native, #408 (11 February 1991) (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - New York Times, September 12, 2001 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Wisdom: The Magazine of Knowledge for Lifetime Learning and Eduction. Vol. 32 Walt Disney., 1959 (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Wisdom: The Magazine of Knowledge for Lifetime Learning and Eduction. Vol. 34 Nehru of India., 1960 (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Wisdom: The Magazine of Knowledge for Lifetime Learning and Eduction. Vol. 36 John Harvard., 1961 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Wisdom: The Magazine of Knowledge for Lifetime Learning and Eduction. Vol. 38 Robert Frost., 1962 (Box 64, Folder 5)
- Oversize Materials: Series X.D: Miscellaneous
  These boxes contain oversize materials from Series X.D: Miscellaneous
  - ACT UP poster, undated (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Bernard Mathys, undated (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Giorno, John, undated (Folder 15)
  - "No Trifling with Love", poster. Play by Alfred de Musset. Directed and Produced by Rudy Laurent., undated (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Penny Arcade publicity poster for event at PS 122, dedicated to Cookie Mueller. July 12-15, undated (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Placemat from a Japanese restaurant in France, French-Japanese translations., undated (Box 64, Folder 2)
- Oversize Materials: Series X.E: Books
  These boxes contain oversize materials from Series X.E: Books
  - Form and Colour: The Mosque of Cordoba, undated (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Avedon, Richard Photographs 1947-1977, 1978 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Breeskin, Adelyn Mary Cassatt advertisement and proposal for a Catalogue raisonne, undated (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Damisch, Hubert and Henry Martin Adami, 1974 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Daniel, Howard, Heronimus Bosch, 1947 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Day, F. Holland Suffering the Ideal, 1995 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Daumien, undated (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Jeff Greenfield, Television: The First Fifty Years, 1977 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Martini, Simon, Pinacoteca de los Genios, undated (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Great Moments of Harper's Bazaar, undated (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Souls Grown Deep: African American Vernacular Art of the South, vol. 1, undated (Box 66)
  - Venini, 1989 (Box 56, Folder 1)